

PROFILE

My name is Rishab Jha. I am from Bihar but resident of Pune. I am in a final year of my graduation course in CSE (B-Tech CSE) from D.Y. Patil International University, Akurdi, Pune. My specialization subject is mostly focused on Data Science but have other interests such as UI Designer, Cyber Security and Frontend Developer. As a computer science student, I have good problem-solving skills as well as hands on practice in various technical fields.

SKILLS

Data Scientist

Data Analyst

Power BI/Excel

Data Visualization

UI & UX Design

Python/C/C++/ R

Microsoft Office Suite Frontend Developer

HTML / CSS / PHP

MySQL

Web Scrapping

ACCOMPLISHMENT

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1 WJDxjl123D2QO7Z2AAZHUJgZlE-IY09U?usp=sharing

PERSONAL INFO

Location: Pune, Maharashtra **Phone:** +91 8446565099

E-mail: rishabjha0999@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/rishab09

GitHub:

https://github.com/Rishab-09

Hacker Rank:

https://www.hackerrank.com/Rishab09

Portfolio:

https://rishab-09.github.io/mywebsite/

Known Languages: English, Hindi, Marathi

Date of Birth: 9 June, 2001

Rishab Jha

Data Scientist || Data Analyst || Front-End Developer || Python / C

EDUCATION

2019 June -2023 July

B-TECH- Computer Science

- D. Y. Patil International University.
- Year of completion: Currently Pursuing.

2017 Jun -2019 July

HIGH SCHOOL (XII) - Science

- Sant Tukaram High School & Jr. College (STATE
- Year of completion: 2019
- Percentage: 69.85%

2015 Jun -2017 July

SCHOOL (X)

- Nirmal Bethany High School (STATE BOARD)
 - Year of completion: 2017
- Percentage: 81.00%



WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Annotation (AI/ML):

STRATA UNISON (New York) | Apr 2022 - Ongoing

Responsibilities during the internship is to perform data annotation on the given dataset that are going to be used to train machine learning model.

Web & App Development:

Ananta Resource Management | Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

Worked on two different application using Microsoft power app and also using android studio and flutter as well as WIX website.

Campus Ambassador:

NEO Educational Foundation | Apr 2021 - May 2021

Spread awareness about the National Engineering Olympiad exam with the help of different social media platforms like WhatsApp, Instagram and Facebook.

National LinkedIn Strategic Planner:

Youth India Foundation | Apr 2021 - Jul 2021

Making strategy about how to make the company on top and to spread awareness about YIF using social media platforms.



PROJECTS

JARVIS-A Python ChatBot

Worked on a project to build a chatbot which works on knowledge-based concepts like playing YouTube or Chrome or sending message to someone on WhatsApp.

DYPIU Library Created a library website based on the concept of DBMS which performs simple functions like storing the books and keeping the track of the books issued and many more.

Data Analysis/ ML Algorithm Performed various statistical operation and exploratory data analysis on the dataset. Also, used various techniques and steps from data pre-processing to build model developing to predict

Targeted Advertisement & Marketing Analytics

Performed ML techniques on the dummy dataset where the model will suggest the ads based on the interest and spending times on Instagram reels